Finding Aid for the Colman Andrews Papers LSC.1428
UCLA Library Special Collections
Colman Andrews papers
1958-1996
UCLA Library Special Collections
Andrews, Colman
LSC.1428
1 unknown (1 oversize box)
13.5 Linear Feet (27 boxes)
Colman Andrews wrote Best Restaurants, Los Angeles and Southern California (with others, c. 1978), Best Restaurants Los Angeles (c. 1984) and Catalan Cuisine: Europe's Last Great Culinary Secret (1988). The collection consists of Andrews' manuscripts, correspondence, notes, published articles, printed and photocopied articles, and the typed manuscript, advance proof, and paperback edition of Catalan Cuisine: Europe's Last Great Culinary Secret in English and Catalan.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Colman Andrews, 1985, 2000.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942303223606533
Biography
Colman Andrews grew up in Southern California and graduated from UCLA with a Bachelor of Arts degree in History and Philosophy in 1969. He wrote Catalan cuisine: Europe's last great culinary secret (1988), Everything on the table: plain talk about food and wine (1992), and Flavors of the Riviera (1996); he co-authored and edited Saveur cooks authentic American (1998), Saveur cooks authentic French (1999), and Saveur cooks authentic Italian (2001); he contributed to the books, Malaparte: a house like me (1999), and Setting the American table: essays for the new culture of food and wine (2001); as well as over 2500 freelance articles (1966-2004) on food, wine, and the arts. His articles have appeared in Bon Appetit, the Chicago Sun-Times, Christian science monitor, Creem, Food & wine, the Hollywood reporter, Los Angeles magazine, the Los Angeles press, the Los Angeles Times, the Mail on Sunday (UK), Metropolitan home, Musica jazz (Italy), Phonograph record magazine, the Radio times (UK), Travel leisure, and the Sunday Telegraph magazine (UK). Andrews has won numerous awards for his writing and was one of the first 50 recipients named in Who's Who of Cooking in America (1985).
Scope and Content
The bulk of the collection consists of typescripts of articles, reviews, short stories and screenplays written by Colman Andrews. Included are magazine and newspaper clippings of articles written for the Los Angeles Times, as well as many music, food and travel articles written during the 1970s and 1980s. There are biographies of jazz and rock musicians from the 1960s and 1970s and reviews of live performances. The collection contains the setting copies and drafts for Catalan cuisine (1988-1989), Listener's guide to jazz (1980), Everything on the table (1991-1992), Appetites and attitudes (no date), and Flavors of the Riviera (1996) as well as a paperback copy of Catalan cuisine (1988) and Cocina Catalan (1989) by Colman Andrews. Also included are general correspondence, correspondence between Andrews and various editors, and related business correspondence. There is a small amount of material of his writings as a child, material from his college days, and articles on the various subjects in which he collected.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series and sub-series:
Collected by Colman Andrews
Magazine clippings
Magazines
Correspondence
Itinerary
Magazines
Newspaper clippings
Recipes
Writings by Colman Andrews
Articles
Biography
Book reviews
Books
Food
Magazine clippings
Music--biography
Music--live performance reviews
Music--record labels
Music--record reviews
Poetry
Restaurant reviews
Restaurant reviews--book (Best restaurants)
Stories/screenplays
Theatre review
Travel
Wine
Wine--magazine clippings
Authors, American -- 20th century -- Archives.; Manuscripts for publication; Cookery, Spanish -- Catalonian style.; Andrews, Colman--Archives.
- Collected by Colman Andrews
  - Jean de Belley, 1974 October (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Loyola notebook, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Untitled manuscript, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Scope and Contents note
    Untitled writings by Colman Andrews
  - Miscellaneous clippings, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Romantic dining & travel letter, 1983 December (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Ten recommended Parisian restaurants
  - Auberge des deux signes, 1983 July (Box 2, Folder 56)
    "Perfect" Paris restaurant? (The), 2 copies
  - Bobby Womack - communication, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Record album insert, includes biography and line art
  - Ornette Coleman, Horace Silver, Elvin Jones, Donald Byrd, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Blue Note record album insert, includes biography
  - Magazine clippings
    - New West California Rstaurant Guide, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      p. 43-50, 2 copies
  - Magazines
    - New West, 1979 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      vol. 4, no. 10, 2 copies
- Correspondence
  - 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 1975 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - 1976 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - 1979 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - 1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - 1981 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - 1982 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - 1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - 1984 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - 1985 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - 1986 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - 1987 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - 1988 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - 1989 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - 1990 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - undated (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Coast Magazine, 1972 July-1975 September 24 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Domino, 1988 April 4-1989 May 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - New West, 1978 November 27-1979 July 27 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Bon Appetit, 1976 May 17-1989 August 11 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Food & Wine, 1981 June 3-1989 October 20 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Travel & Leisure, 1973 November 11-1989 December 7 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Apartment Llife, 1978 July 12-1980 November 14 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Home, 1981 January 29-1989 December 28 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Itinerary
  - New York - Europe trip, 1988 February 17-1988 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New York trip, 1987 December 23-1988 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco, Napa, Sonoma trip, 1988 July 15-1988 July 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - U.S. trip, 1988 March 12-1988 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco, Seattle, Portland trip, 1988 September 12-1988 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - New York, New Jersey, Boston trip, 1989 September 30-1989 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - New York, Europe trip, 1988 April 1-1988 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Magazines
  - Prints: Low-cost way to a home art gallery, Winter 1969/1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Continental (The), vol. 10, no. 1, p. 6, 2 copies
  - Where to go from Los Angeles, Fall 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Budget travel, vol. 2, no. 3, p. 26-29, 76-79
  - Foreign money game, 1975 May-1975 June (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Odyssey, vol. 8, no. 3, p. 9-12
  - Monterey: A look at the real California, 1975 November-1975 December (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Odyssey, vol. 8, no. 6, p. 6-10, 3 copies
  - Re-emergence of fascism (The), book review, 1968 October (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Mankind, vol. 1, no. 9, p. 64
  - Short history of wine (A), 1971 October (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Mankind, vol. 3, no. 3, p. 34-41, 2 copies
  - Eldest son of genius: the story of Henry Rousseau (The), 1975 October (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Mankind, vol. 5, no. 3, p. 36-41
  - Hollywood consumer guide (The) and Pointer Sisters (The), 1974 August (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Creem, vol. 6, no. 3, p. 46, 70
  - Szabo a L.A., 1973 April (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Musica Jazz, vol. 29, no. 4
- Newspaper clippings
  - Creem, 1972 April-1975 November (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Includes 1 photocopy of clipping
  - L.A. Times (roundabout and you), 1976 February 14-1979 December 23 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Includes photocopies of clippings
  - Ojai Valley News (The), 1961 February 2-1961 October 16 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Flyer, 1971 October 14-1972 May 25 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - L.A. Times book review, 1975 November 23-1977 May 22 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Showcase/Chicago Sun Times, 1969 December 7-1975 February 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Loyola University of Los Angeles, 1962 November 19-1962 December 10 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Ventura (Calif.) County Star-Free Press (The), 1961 February 1 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Coast Magazine, L.A., undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Prestige records reprint
  - UCLA Summer Bruin, 1970 July 10 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles Free Press, 1965 October 1-1977 January 20 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Music World, 1972 November-1973 June (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Christian Science Monitor, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Ampersand, 1977 October-1982 December (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Soul and Jazz, 1974 April-1977 September (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Zoo World, 1974 December 5 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Phonograph Records Magazine, 1971 August-1978 March (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Staff (The), (Mr. Food), 1971 October 8-1972 July 13 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Daily Planet, 1970 July-1970 September (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Daily Planet, 1970 October-1970 December (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Daily Planet, 1971 January-1971 May (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Daily Planet, 1971 June-1971 December (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Recipes
  - Winter salads, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous recipes, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Writings by Colman Andrews
  - Resume, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous notes and writings, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - KLAC, June 18 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Juvenalia, ca. 1958-1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Best restaurants, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    correspondence, clippings, etc.
  - Books read by Colman Robert Andrews, 1961 June-1962 January (Box 23, Folder 38)
    With comments which are prejudiced and strongly opinionated
  - Re: Loyola University, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Wildcat (The), 1959 December 4-1960 October 14 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - "People" magazine, 1958 June (Box 23, Folder 41)
    vol. 1, no. 1
  - Crossword, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Articles
    - How to buy a rug, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Waiter, there's a flaw in my soup (one restaurant critic's pet peeves), undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Nouvelle nightmare (A) -- revised, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Three reasons why I hate being a restaurant critic and you probably wouldn't like it either, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - How I became a homeowner, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - American hot wax, March 23 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - The Rumanian cinema - maturity after fifty?, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Masters of the esperanto cinema, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Film news, 1969 April (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Women's rodeo, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Backgammon - kid's game... or is it?, 1973 August (Box 23, Folder 14)
      PSA, p. 37-40
    - Backgammon, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Crying, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Men who get films started (The): power in the new Hollywood, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - How to tell if your man is fooling around, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - What turns men on, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Subjective seascape, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Saunas, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Amputee films, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Finnish films, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Fear factor (The), 1979 April 23 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      Photocopy of clipping
    - Guns, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
      For New West Magazine
    - Art, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Appetites, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
      Various articles
    - Word of mouth #3, #13, and #16, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Zino Mouton-Cadet cigars, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Food magazine, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Food and wine institute, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Sandbox to the stars, 1971 November (Box 23, Folder 32)
      Ford Times, vol. 64, no. 11, p. 8-14, 2 originals, 1 photocopy
    - Germany and the Iron Guard, 1930-1940, 1970 June (Box 23, Folder 33)
      Undergraduate journal of history (The), vol. 1, no. 1, p. 11-26
    - Germany and the Iron Guard, 1930-1940, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Ad Reinhardt: the artist as phenomenologist, 1969 May (Box 23, Folder 35)
      Undergraduate journal of philosophy (The), vol. 1, no. 1, p. 39-44
    - Megarian and non-megarian modal terms: some metaphysical considerations, 1970 January (Box 23, Folder 36)
      Undergraduate journal of philosophy (The), vol. 2, no. 1, p. 17-24
    - Metaphysical implications of megarian and non-megarian modal terms, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Biography
    - Larry Flynt, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Irina Petrscu and Iurie Darie, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Francois Truffaut, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Sulleyman the magnificent, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Like...Charles, 1962 May (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Jazz report, vol. 2, no. 9, p. 13
    - David Wilkie, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Ad Reinhardt - the artist as phenomenologist, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Ernest Miller Hemingway, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Robert Evans: a view from the top, 1977 September 11 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      Newsday, LI interview (The), 3 copies
    - Alex Madonna, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - William Shatner, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Wonder Woman -- Lynda Carter, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Jean Bertranou, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Zerah Colburn, Spring 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      New England galaxy (The), vol. 13, no. 4, p. 15-19
    - Viva Moreau (Jeanne Moreau), undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Ken Frank, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Leonard Nimoy, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Six Los Angeles artists, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Marta Feuchtwanger/the Oppermans, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Hot people -- Lydia Shire, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - What's cooking in the melting pot, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
      World of flavor from L.A.'s best chefs (A)
    - David Hockney, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - John Thorne, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
      By phone to MH
    - Bob Waggoner -- Hotel de la Poste, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Wolfgang Puck, Inc., undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Alain Senderens -- Guy Savoy, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Alain Dutournier, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Jean Bardet, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Silva/mirror to America, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Le Divellec/Duquesnoy, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Le Vieux Moulin/La Tamarissiere, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Sam Lopata/Adam Tihany, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Mariscal, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Julia Morgan, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Kenji Seki, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
      To MH by phone
    - Cooking class -- Gary Darling, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Thomas Catherall (cooking class), undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - John Makin, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Patrick Healy (nicoise food), undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Colman Robert Andrews, 1962 September-1962 October (Box 21, Folder 40)
      Jazz report, vol. 3, no. 1 and 2, p. 19
  - Book reviews
    - Miscellaneous book reviews, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - L.A. times book reviews, 1976 March 14-1977 June 26 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      Newspaper clippings and copy of clipping
    - Best food books -- revised (by phone to MH), undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Fire and ice by Andrew Tobias, 1976 August 27 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Klynt's law by Elliot Baker, 1976 June 4 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Cheap chic by Catherine Milinaire, 1975 December (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Love stories selected by Martin Levin, 1975 October 24 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      2 copies
    - Don (The) by William Brashler, 1977 March 9 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Ou est le garlic, or French cooking in 50 lessons by Len Deighton, 1977 March 30 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Twins, by Bari Wood and Jack Geasland, 1977 May 3 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Horseless rider (The) by Barbara Burn, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
      Book brief for new west magazine
    - Judith Krantz/"Scruples", undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Final fire (The) by Dennis Smith, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Shibumi by Trevanian, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
      Book brief for New West magazine
    - Old muddle of the new riddle of induction (The), undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - In the city of the olesha fruit by Norman Dubie, undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Clan of the cave bear (The) by Jean M. Auel, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
      Book review for New West magazine
    - Hollywood babylon by Kenneth Anger, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Dreams of a young girl by Alain Robbe-Grillet, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
      Magazine clipping
    - Dreams of a young girl by Alain Robbe-Grillet, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Heartbreak hotel by Anne Rivers Siddons, 1976 September 24 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Up the city of the angels by Liza Williams, undated (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Mubadele: an Ottoman-Russian exchange of ambassadors by Norman Itzkowitz and Max Mote, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Foreign policy of Hitler's Germany; diplomatic revolution in Europe, 1933-36 (The), undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
      By Gerhard L. Weinberg
    - Musical stages by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Labor radical, from the wobblies to CI0, undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Great book of wine (The), undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Monsieur by Lawrence Durrell, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Books
    - Catalan cuisine, 1988 February 23-1988 February 25; [2 folders.] (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      p. 373-785
    - Catalan cuisine, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Cocina Catalan, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Catalan cuisine -- setting copy, 1988; [4 folders.] (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
      folder 1: p. i-200
      folder 2: p. 201-340
      folder 3: p. 341-543
      folder 4: p. 544-785
    - Catalan cuisine -- uncorrected advance proof, 1988 June (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Listener's guide to jazz, undated (Box 16, Folder 1-4, Box 17)
      box 16/folder 1: p. i-70, including new pages; multiple copies
      box 16/folder 2: p. 71-163; multiple copies
      box 16/folder 3: p. 164-250; multiple copies
      box 16/folder 4: p. 251-337; multiple copies
      box 17/folder 1: p. 338-444; multiple copies
      box 17/folder 2: p. 445-535; multiple copies
    - Listener's guide to jazz, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Corrected galleys, etc
    - Everything on the table, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 4-5, Box 18)
      box 17/folder 4: p. 1-150
      box 17/folder 5: p. 151-277
      box 18/folder 1: p. 278-444
      box 18/folder 2: p. 445-583
      box 18/folder 3: new and miscellaneous pages
    - Everything on the table -- setting copy, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 4-6, Box 19)
      box 18/folder 4: p. i-162
      box 18/folder 5: p. 163-309
      box 18/folder 6: p. 1-191
      box 19/folder 1: p. 192-390
      box 19/folder 2: p. 391-583
    - Appetites and attitudes -- original, undated (Box 19, Folder 3-5)
      box 19/folder 3: p. i-182
      box 19/folder 4: p. 183-381
      box 19/folder 5: p. 382-550
    - Flavors of the riviera, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
      box 20/folder 2: p. i-179
      box 20/folder 3: p. 180-383
  - Food
    - Cooking with beaujolais nouveau, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Too many tomatoes, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Moroccan salads, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Paella amb verdures (paella with vegetables), undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Ice cream, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Mexican food, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Tapas, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Fungus among us, or me and my mushroom tree (A), undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Truth in dining, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Potatoes, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Dim sum, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Demystifying pepper, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Italian food: trentino/alto adige, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - French menus, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Vietnamese food, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Blue cheese, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Olive oil, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
      For Apartment Life Magazine
    - Secrets of the city -- Washington D.C. hotel, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Boy food, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Cookbooks -- revised, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Recreation cooking, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Trouble with newcomers..., undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Oysters of Oualidia (The) -- revised, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Healthy dining in Los Angeles, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Oysters of Casablanca (The), undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Burmese food, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Muesli euro-breakfast, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Magazine clippings
    - From the bathtub to the boudoir gin, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
      p. 63-64
    - All the tea lunch in China, 1977 April (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Chic, p. 61-64, 93-94, 99-100
    - Grand motel, 1977 April (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Chic, p. 9-12, 2 copies
    - Brilliant idea no. 8, 1977 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Chic, p. 8
    - America's grape grandees, 1977 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Chic, p. 39-42, 79-82
    - Vive Le, 1977 August (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Chic, p. 72-74, 91-92
    - Inside scoop (The), 1977 September (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Chic, p. 83-84
    - Thai-one on, 1977 September (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Chic, p. 71-72
    - California white, 1977 October (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Chic, p. 82-84
    - After dinner upstarts, 1977 December (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Chic, p. 69-70, 2 copies
    - Pop your cork, 1978 January (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Chic, p. 41-42
    - Hangover helpers, 1978 February (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Chic, p. 81-82
    - California wines, 1978 March (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Chic, p. 77-78, 99-100
    - Anise in wonderland, 1978 April (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Chic, p. 75-76
    - Best head in the world (The), 1978 May (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Chic, p. 43-44
    - Wine cocktails, 1978 July (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Chic, p. 81-82, 2 copies
    - Summer smoothies, 1978 August (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Chic, p. 33-34
    - Liquidators (The), 1978 October (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Chic, p. 73-74, 99-100
    - Port report, 1978 November (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Chic, p. 71-72, 91-92
    - Vin & vigor, 1978 December (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Chic, p. 45-46, 101-102
    - Hot stuff, 1979 January (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Very sherry, 1979 February (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Chic, p. 85-86
    - Dare to be grape, 1979 April (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Chic, p. 83-86
    - "Hey Porter!", 1979 May (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Chic, p. 67-68, 93-94
    - Pop wines sans regret, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
      p. 53-58
    - Estranged Etta James (The), May/June (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Phonograph Record Magazine, p. 37-42, 2 copies
    - Straight from the hip, 1979 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      p. 6
    - Edwards e monk al shelly manne's, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Musica Jazz, p. 25-26
    - Cool jazz finds a home in L.A., undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
      p. 56-58
    - Rumanian film today (The), 1969 August-1969 September (Box 2, Folder 30)
      East Europe, p. 21-24
    - Oui, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Musician, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Mainliner, 1974 April-1974 June (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Hollywood reporter (The), 1972 February 2-1972 August 31 (Box 2, Folder 34)